C:/Users/Jim/Documents/BioWare/Dragon Age/addins/af_archid/module/override/	af_archid_en-us.tlk
6610001	No Helmet Rulebook
6610002	The character using this book will toggle on/off helmet graphics.
6610003	"WARNING!  The No_Helmet_Hack module failed to hide the helmets.  This is likely due to an incompatibility with a loaded module.  Possible solutions:
1)  Check the My Documents/Bioware/Packages/Core/Overrides file for any BITM_* file.  Delete it if there is, as this would be the likely conflicting mod.
2)  Remove this mod and reinstall it as the last mod
3)  Remove other mods until this mod succeeds.  Suspect mods that change item properties.
4)  Download and install the master override file."
6610004	Party Storage Chest
6610005	"<name/> (<guitypename/>)
<usetype/>

<description/>"
6610006	"<name/> (<guitypename/>)
<usetype/>
Range: <range/>
Activation: <cost/>
Cooldown: <cooldown/>s

<requirements/>

<description/>"
6610007	"<name/> (<guitypename/>)
<usetype/>
Range: <range/>
Activation: <cost/>
Cooldown: <cooldown/>s

<description/>"
6610008	Arcane Unlock
6610009	A short burst of arcane magic will deal with most simple locks.
6610010	Finesse Unlock
6610011	More stubborn locks require some finesse. This spell is able to manipulate some of the inner components allowing opening of more complex locks.
6610012	Power Unlock
6610013	"This spell allows you to channel more of your power into the lock, opening more complex varieties."
6610014	Spell too weak to unlock
6610015	Lock cannot be unlocked with magic
6610016	Wrong type of target to unlock
6610017	Target already unlocked
89120084	Spider Cave
89120086	Cave Exit
89120087	Queen Spider
89120090	"You have killed some spiders guarding a cluster of cocoons. One of the cocoons seems to be moving slightly, and making a muffled noise."
89120091	You have killed all the spiders and found Arbither's father's body.
89120093	"You have returned Arbither's father's possessions to her. She was especially pleased to receive his twin swords.

Once she has had time to bury her father, she asks that you come to see her in Lothering Chantry as she has need of further help."
89120095	You have recovered an amulet and a pair of very smart swords from Ser Nathan's body.
89120096	"Ser Arbither has rewarded you for rescuing her, but you have declined to help her recover her father's body."
89120097	You have stolen Ser Arbither's swords from her.
89120099	You have rescued Ser Arbither Cora of Lothering from a spider's cocoon.
89120100	"You have killed Ser Arbither Cora, along with many of the Templars who were guarding refugees in Lothering.

On the plus side, you have gained a very nice pair of swords."
89120102	You have stolen Ser Arbither's swords from her - she is bitterly angry but unable to do anything about it.
89120104	Spiders & Knives
89120105	Spider Cave
89120107	"Ser Arbither Cora, knight of Lothering, is missing. She was last seen heading toward Spider Cave, north of Lothering.

Ser Arbither is a well-respected knight, whose like is needful in these troubled times. Her friends are offering a reward for word of her whereabouts, for her rescue, or for recovery of her body."
89120108	"<emp>Rescue Ser Arbither Cora</emp>

You read on the job board about a Lothering knight who has gone missing. A reward will be paid to anyone who finds/rescues her."
89120109	"<emp>Find Ser Arbither's Father</emp>

You have rescued Ser Arbither from a spider's cocoon. She is going to the Chantry, but has asked you to find her father's body and effects."
89120110	Ser Arbither has rewarded you for rescuing her from the spiders.
89120111	"<emp>Too Late To Rescue Ser Arbither Cora</emp>

With the destruction of Lothering, the fate of Ser Arbither Cora remains a mystery."
89120112	Rescue Ser Arbither
89120113	"A request from Ser Arbither Cora, knight of Lothering:

Darkspawn have overrun Knife Edge Manor, my family home. In the absence of my father, who is missing, presumed dead, I call for the assistance of a hero who will help me retake the manor, and rescue certain artefacts held within.

If you are that hero, meet me in Lothering Chantry to plan our attack.

This is a dangerous mission, and the reward will be commensurate."
89120114	"<emp>Retake Knife Edge</emp>

You read on the job board about a Lothering knight who seeks help in retaking her manor from the darkspawn."
89120115	"<emp>Speak to Ser Arbither cora</emp>

You have helped Ser Arbither retake her manor, and should speak to her for your reward."
89120116	Ser Arbither Cora has rewarded you for your help in retaking her manor.
89120117	"<emp>Too Late To Retake Knife Edge</emp>

With the destruction of Lothering, it seems unlikely that you will be able to contact Ser Arbither Cora."
89120118	"You have arrived at Knife Edge, Ser Arbither Cora's manor."
89120119	Retake Knife Edge
89120120	Cave Exit
89120122	Cocooned Body
89120124	Ser Nathan Cora
89120125	"Shrouded in spider silk, this dessicated corpse looks almost lifelike, but somehow ... wrong!"
89120126	Ser Nathan's Amulet
89120127	This amulet is intricately carved with a coat of arms.
89120128	Ser Arbither Cora
89120129	"Very aristocratic, maybe a little snooty, but she looks tough, with a slightly wild glint in her eyes."
89120130	"<desc>This cocoon appears to be moving slightly, and there are muffled noises coming from it</desc>"
89120131	<desc>A figure falls out of the cocoon</desc>
89120132	<desc>After a moment the movement and noises die down</desc>
89120133	<desc>The movement and noises intensify</desc>
89120134	<desc>This cocoon is now empty</desc>
89120135	<act>Cut the cocoon open</act>
89120137	<desc>Silently watch the cocoon</desc>
89120138	Is there anyone in there?
89120139	<desc>Leave the cocoon alone</desc>
89120141	The Crane
89120143	The Crow
89120145	"I say, I am most awfully grateful. It was dashed unpleasant in there."
89120146	"I'm Arbither Cora, don't you know, but you can call me 'Knives' - most folk do."
89120147	Are you game to finish the job? Of course you are! My Father's remains are somewhere further in.
89120148	"So kill the rest of those leggy blighters for me, and bring me his effects, and I'll see it's worth your while."
89120149	"Got to get to the Chantry now, before these bally eggs hatch. Meet me there. Maker speed!"
89120150	"Wonderful, you made it! Did you manage to find my poor father?"
89120151	I'm grateful to you. And have you brought me his things?
89120152	Excellent fellow! You deserve your reward for that.
89120153	Now the spiders are gone I can arrange to have my father's body recovered.
89120154	"But come back later, I've got a job that'll be just up your street. Maker's blessings!"
89120155	Good chap! I'll wait for you here.
89120156	"Oh! Very well, here is your reward. If you change your mind, I'll be here for a  while."
89120157	Jolly good show! We showed those filthy darkspawn!
89120158	"I said you'd be rewarded, and so you shall."
89120159	"You helped me get my father's swords, here's an item of my mother's that I'm sure will be of use."
89120160	"The labourer is worthy of his hire,  as they say."
89120161	"Maker willing, this place should be somewhere for the templars to fall back to when Lothering falls."
89120162	"This place is bally filthy! I must get some servants in, those elves are so good at cleaning!"
89120163	"Hail, stout hero! Are you ready to help retake Knife Edge from the filthy darkspawn?"
89120164	Good show! Let us be on our way.
89120165	Good day to you.
89120171	"Yes, the spiders had killed him. They're dead now."
89120172	I found his medallion and swords for you.
89120176	"No, I had to come out for supplies. I'll return shortly."
89120178	No. I've rescued you and that's enough.
89120186	I am indeed.
89120204	"<desc>Shrouded in spider silk, this dessicated corpse looks almost lifelike, but somehow ... wrong!</desc>"
89120206	Knife Edge
89120208	Knife Edge
89120209	"Ser Arbither Cora's home, near the road to Redcliffe"
89120214	The Crane
89120216	The Crow
89120218	Knotwood Staff
89120219	This gnarled staff's origin can be traced back to the Knotwood Hills. No doubt it once belonged to a hangman's tree or worse; a darkspawn scratching pole!
89120220	Thunderer
89120221	The unusual design of this heavy one-handed weapon appears to be of foreign origin. The air around the head of the weapon crackles with electrical energy.
89120222	HjorrMikill
89120223	"HjorMikill' means GreatSword in an ancient language. 
Protected by the mountains and snow, this sword was probably forged for a King when the elders were young, to protect in troubled times."
89120224	Dagger of Ashyera's Followers
89120225	These daggers - though they're scarce in Ferelden - are commonly wielded by a sect within a petty state of the Free Marches.
89120228	"<emp>Meet Ser Arbither In The Chantry</emp>

You have rescued Ser Arbither from a spider's cocoon, and found her father's body and effects. Meet her in the Chantry for your reward."
89120230	"I do hope you'll pop in when we're ship-shape again, old chap. I'll put a chest in the Hunter's Room for your use."
89120233	"You have accompanied Ser Arbither Cora to Knife Edge, her manor."
89120234	You have succeeded in helping Ser Arbither Cora recapture her manor from the darkspawn.
89120235	"Your quest to regain Knife Edge for Ser Arbither Cora is complete. She has indicated that you are welcome to return at any time, and that she will keep a chest there for your use."
89120236	"<emp>Lothering is lost</emp>

Lothering has been overrun by darkspawn. You do not know whether Ser Arbither Cora has perished or escaped; whatever happened, she did it without your help."
89120237	Knife Edge
89120244	Filthy darkspawn! What have they done to my home?
89120245	"You have accepted a quest concerning Ser Arbither Cora, knight of Lothering."
89120261	May the maker have mercy upon your shrivelled soul!
89120262	Drat! Something must have moved them: I'll have to search.
89120263	Here is your reward for what you've done.
89120264	I don't believe you! You're a bally liar - hand those swords over now!
89120265	Thank you . Here is your reward.
89120266	Templars! Help me!
89120267	"One day you'll face the Maker's justice, you bally thief!"
89120268	<desc>Lie</desc>All he had on him was this medallion.
89120271	"Very well, here you are."
89120273	"No way, you'll have to fight for them."
89120275	<desc>Threaten</desc>You can have his medallion but the swords are mine!
89120277	Ser Bryant
89120279	Ser Varal
89120281	Templar
89120283	"Very well, if you change your mind, I'll be here for a  while."
89120284	"Greetings, have you changed your mind about finding my father?"
89120285	Jolly good show! Maker go with you.
89120286	You don't scare me! You're a bally thief - hand those swords over now!
89120289	"No, I think I've done enough."
89120291	"Yes, I'll go and look now."
89120297	Templar
89120299	Good day to you.
89120301	Ser Arbither Cora is dead.
89120303	Knife Edge DS
89120304	"Ser Arbither Cora's home, near the road to Redcliffe - attacked by darkspawn."
89120306	"Spiders like fresh meat for their spiderlings, don't you know? <desc>Shudder</desc> Anyway, did you find my poor father?"
89120308	What did you mean earlier about eggs hatching?
89120309	You have taken Ser Arbither's swords as your reward for rescuing her.
89120313	Cook
89120320	Spiders & Knives
89120321	A simple job to earn a few coins ... but where's the client?
89120323	I just need to make some preparations first.
627214943	Spell Shaping
627214944	"When active, the caster will shape and direct wide-area spells to avoid friendly fire at a cost of additional mana. Party members gain protection from the damage, with the additional mana spent based on the number of allies in the target area."
627214945	Improved Spell Shaping
627214946	"Party members gain protection from the secondary effects of friendly spells such as knockdown, freezing and slow movement rate."
627214947	Expert Spell Shaping
627214948	Friendly fire damage protection is extended to all allies on the battlefield.
627214949	Master Spell Shaping
627214950	Allies and party members no longer experience any damage or secondary effects from friendly wide-area spells.
627214951	Warning: Spell Shaping Mod has detected a compatibility issue with one of the mods you have installed. Spell Shaping may not work properly.
627214952	Spell Shaping is a new skill mages can invest in to avoid friendly fire.
627214953	Spell Shaping
627214954	Dheuster@gmail.com
627214955	http://social.bioware.com/project/1470/
826465926	I do hope Ser Bryant is safe. He's awfully brave!
826465927	"Welcome to Knife Edge Manor. We've not cleared all the bally mess yet, but the elves are working jolly hard."
826465928	Hail friend! The chest in the Hunter's Room is for your use.
826465931	"Lothering has fallen! Ser Bryant is here, but so many have died!"
826465932	Filthy darkspawn! Why does the Maker allow this?
826465933	Welcome to Knife Edge Manor. For the moment we are safe here.
826465934	"Hail! It's good to see a friend, even in these sad times."
826465943	The Crane. Not much is known about this sword other than it has a twin sword called the Crow. It is said that together they unveil their true power.
826465944	The Crane. Not much is known about this sword other than it has a twin sword called the Crow. It is said that together they unveil their true power.
826465945	The Crow and the Crane are among the less well known artifacts of Ferelden. Both imbued with powerful magic and when wielded together they are said to make their wielder almost invincible.
826465946	The Crow and the Crane are among the less well known artifacts of Ferelden. Both imbued with powerful magic and when wielded together they are said to make their wielder almost invincible.
826465954	Ser Arbither Cora
826465955	"Very aristocratic, maybe a little snooty, but she looks tough, with a slightly wild glint in her eyes."
826465957	"Lothering has fallen! Ser Bryant is here, but so many have died!"
826465958	Filthy darkspawn! Why does the Maker allow this?
826465959	Welcome to Knife Edge Manor. For the moment we are safe here.
826465960	"Hail! It's good to see a friend, even in these sad times."
826465962	I do hope Ser Bryant is safe. He's awfully brave!
826465963	"Welcome to Knife Edge Manor. We've not cleared all the bally mess yet, but the elves are working jolly hard."
826465964	Hail friend! The chest in the Hunter's Room is for your use.
826465972	"Maker willing, this place should be somewhere for the templars to fall back to when Lothering falls."
826465973	"This place is bally filthy! I must get some servants in, those elves are so good at cleaning!"
826465974	"I do hope you'll pop in when we're ship-shape again, old chap. I'll put a chest in the Hunter's Room for your use."
826466002	Good day to you.
826466055	"You have helped Ser Arbither Cora defend Knife Edge. She has indicated that you are welcome to return at any time, and that she will keep a chest there for your use."
826466056	Knife Edge
826466065	Oh you hero! What wonderful timing the maker has!
826466066	Darkspawn are coming! Prepare yourself; they'll be here any second!
826466075	"Oh my, that was a hard fought battle. Jolly well done!"
826466076	"Isn't Ser Bryant wonderful! So brave, and so handsome!"
826466077	Isn't Ser Bryant wonderful!
826466078	"Ser Bryant and I are to be married once this is all over, Maker willing!"
826466079	Please come to our wedding!
826466080	"Hail! It's good to see a friend, even in these sad times."
826466081	"Hail friend, welcome to Knife Edge Manor! The chest in the Hunter's Room is for your use."
826466090	Did you just...?
826466091	The people here have precious little. That so many resort to thievery makes matters all the worse.
826466092	"So stop it, right now."
826466093	"We are watching you carefully, stranger. Very carefully."
826466103	Please do not cause a disturbance. Matters are delicate enough with all the newcomers.
826466104	We are here to guard this chantry and all mankind from forbidden magics.
826466105	"You are welcome here, so long as you cause no trouble."
826466106	There is something... odd about you. I trust that you are not here to make trouble.
826466107	"Greetings, and welcome to the chantry."
826466117	"There's word of darkspawn stragglers, but no sign of the main horde."
826466118	"We are the only hope of protection this village has now, and I will <emp>not</emp> abandon them."
826466119	That is all. May the Maker have mercy on us.
826466126	"I see you have returned, Sister. I thought you had left the chantry for good."
826466127	"I have, Ser Bryant."
826466128	I see. Is there something more I can do for you?
826466129	"And who is the lady with you, if I might ask?"
826466130	"And who is the gentleman with you, if I might ask?"
826466132	"Greetings, Grey Warden. What can I do for you?"
826466133	"Hello, again. What can I do for you?"
826466135	"Yes, my lady? Who might you be?"
826466136	"I... see. I am Ser Bryant, commander of the Lothering templars."
826466137	"Teyrn Loghain declared all Grey Wardens traitors, responsible for the king's death. You know this, I hope?"
826466138	And set a bounty on any who survived.
826466139	"I don't believe the Grey Wardens would be as careless or malicious as the teyrn claims, but either way, there it is."
826466140	"It is best you not linger, though. Just... in case."
826466141	"Even if I had no other concerns, I would not seek to collect the bounty."
826466142	"I am Ser Bryant, commander of Lothering's remaining templars."
826466143	You don't seem like the other refugees. Are you one of Arl Eamon's knights?
826466144	I'd tell you what I told the others: Nothing here will assist your quest. The Urn of Sacred Ashes is a myth.
826466145	A mythical relic of Andraste.
826466146	"One of the arl's knights, Ser Donall, is here searching for fantasies while…"
826466147	Never mind. Ask him if you care about this foolishness.
826466148	"If the matter is important, certainly."
826466149	The revered mother leads this flock; I merely command her templars.
826466150	"Normally, our role is to protect the chantry and seek out unsanctioned magic. For now, it is all we can do to protect the innocent."
826466151	As am I.
826466152	<desc>Sigh</desc> I have no time to even think about such things right now.
826466153	My concern is protecting these people. I see nothing threatening them other than the darkspawn.
826466154	"Let us pretend that I was such a mage. What would you do to me, hmm?"
826466155	"We have more than swords at our disposal. We are taught to dispel unholy magics, as well."
826466156	If only our powers worked to keep away the darkspawn. Alas it is not so.
826466157	"In her study, no doubt, preparing what she will take when we eventually evacuate."
826466158	"Our bann was summoned by Teyrn Loghain, and he took his soldiers north with him. Lothering has been abandoned."
826466159	"You have met her? She came to the chantry years ago, to begin a new life of contemplation."
826466160	"Yesterday, however, she packed up and left the chantry. Forever, she said."
826466161	"I assume she was fleeing the darkspawn, like the rest of us."
826466162	I don't think her life before she arrived was a happy one.
826466163	"She was never well suited to the life here, but I do believe her faith in the Maker was sincere."
826466164	Of course.
826466169	Other than the darkspawn horde bearing down on us?
826466170	"None of it is good. Teyrn Loghain is set to declare himself king, I hear. Disaster piled on disaster."
826466171	"Teyrn Loghain has no legitimate claim on the throne. He may be a hero, and his daughter may be queen, but he is a commoner and the king's corpse is barely cold."
826466172	"If Arl Eamon was able to intervene, perhaps it would not have gone this far."
826466173	I do not care who takes the throne. Only fools fight over who owns a cottage while it burns down around them.
826466174	None that we know of.
826466175	"I suppose since you are a mage, I do know something that might interest you."
826466176	Don't look surprised. I would be a poor templar if I couldn't tell that much.
826466177	"I have heard word that the templars who watch over the Circle of Magi's tower have called for the Right of Annulment. Hopefully, I've heard wrong."
826466178	"If the Right of Annulment is invoked, the tower and every living soul within will be destroyed."
826466179	We need the Circle's help. We should go and find out what's happening.
826466180	Is one of the treaties not with these mages? 'Twould be ironic to have them fricasseed just when they are useful.
826466181	"To have such a call when mages are needed to fight the darkspawn, something terrible must have happened."
826466182	I have nothing else to tell you. The only news <emp>I</emp> care about is the approaching horde.
826466183	Only if you are interested in the business of mages.
826466184	"They are. With the bann having taken his men north, the village is left to its fate."
826466185	We will evacuate as many as we can before the horde reaches us. I will stay as long as I am needed.
826466186	I... see. That is certainly worthy of notice.
826466187	"I cannot openly help you, I fear, but... here, take this key."
826466188	"It opens the large cabinet on the far wall. There is more there than we can carry when we evacuate, so take what you need."
826466189	Maker's breath! How many times must we drive them off?!
826466190	"Well, you won't find it here. We can barely keep control inside the village, much less on the roads. But I will try once more."
826466191	I will not let them take any more advantage of this catastrophe!
826466192	Ser Varal! Those fool bandits have returned. Take some men and drive them off. And see if you can't capture that leader of theirs this time.
826466193	"As you command, Ser Bryant!"
826466194	"Now, unless there's something else you need...?"
826466195	No need. I will have it dealt with... again.
826466196	Indeed? They're gone?
826466197	"It's true. I saw the bastard running for the hills, myself."
826466198	"That's an impressive feat, indeed! Will you accept a small reward for your efforts?"
826466199	"I wish I could afford such help, to be truthful. Take your reward, at any rate... it is all I have to offer."
826466200	"If it interests you, there is a chanter's board outside full of quests that need doing. The chanters even offer pay for some of them."
826466201	That is very generous of you.
826466202	All of them? By yourself?
826466203	It’s true. I saw it from my post. It was over so fast we didn't even have time to get over there.
826466204	"Sad that it needed to come to that, but then they asked for it. Will you accept a small reward for your service?"
826466205	<desc>Sigh</desc> We can barely keep order here in the village.
826466206	"Travel safely, and may the Maker watch over you."
826466207	"I do, though the priests no doubt would tell you otherwise."
826466208	Then what might I do for you?
826466209	I... see.
826466210	"Some have, in recent days."
826466211	"Arl Eamon has fallen ill, and his knights are on a quest for the sacred urn filled with Andraste's ashes, said to cure any malady."
826466212	Arl Eamon is sick? Is it serious?
826466213	"I'm told it's no natural illness. They have found no cure, and thus must chase after miracles."
826466214	He must be very ill if they chase miracles as the only cure.
826466215	It is no trouble. Maker watch over you.
826466216	Yes? Who might you be?
826466228	I am the Grey Warden <FirstName/>.
826466230	The Grey Wardens did no such thing.
826466231	He claimed we're responsible?
826466234	I've heard the rumors.
826466235	You will say nothing about me. Is that clear?
826466237	You can call me <FirstName/>.
826466239	And if I were?
826466240	Have many of his knights come here?
826466241	What is the Urn of Sacred Ashes?
826466244	I need some information.
826466245	Are you in charge here?
826466247	You do know that I am a mage?
826466250	And if you found an unsanctioned mage?
826466252	How do templars fight against magic?
826466254	Where would I find the revered mother?
826466255	Are you the only protection this village has?
826466256	Tell me about something else.
826466257	Can you tell me of Sister Leliana?
826466259	Do you know why she left?
826466260	What kind of person is she?
826466262	Thank you.
826466267	Have you heard any recent news?
826466269	What do you mean?
826466272	What is wrong with Arl Eamon?
826466273	You think there will be civil war?
826466274	King Cailan had no heir?
826466276	Most people consider Teyrn Loghain a hero.
826466277	Have you heard any other news?
826466280	I already know all about this.
826466281	But that means...
826466286	Why? What is the Right of Annulment?
826466287	Do you know why?
826466288	Now? That seems like odd timing.
826466289	I am. Tell me.
826466290	Not really.
826466291	I've nothing else to ask.
826466292	Things seem very dire in the village.
826466295	I'm hoping you can help me. I'm a Grey Warden.
826466297	Is there any other help you can offer?
826466299	About those bandits outside the village...
826466300	They robbed me. I demand compensation!
826466302	[Lie] They robbed me. I demand compensation!
826466303	"They're still there, last I saw."
826466307	"I can do that, if you like."
826466309	One less. I drove them off myself.
826466312	"Certainly, thank you."
826466313	"I could keep an eye out for trouble, for the right pay..."
826466316	No need. Your thanks is enough.
826466318	They won't bother you again. I killed them.
826466321	You need to watch the roads more carefully.
826466323	I should go.
826466325	"You think it's a myth, do you?"
826466327	Well I'm not one of his knights.
826466328	"No, I'm not."
826466329	"I'm a Grey Warden, actually."
826466331	Do many of his knights come here?
826466337	Nobody of importance.
826466338	Pardon me. I didn't mean to interrupt.
826466341	Genlock
826466343	Hurlock
826466345	Hurlock Emissary
826466347	Shriek
826466349	Knotwood Staff (Enhanced)
826466350	This gnarled staff's origin can be traced back to the Knotwood Hills. No doubt it once belonged to a hangman's tree or worse; a darkspawn scratching pole!
826466351	Dagger of Ashyera's Followers (Enhanced)
826466352	These daggers - though they're scarce in Ferelden - are commonly wielded by a sect within a petty state of the Free Marches.
826466354	Ser Nathan's Amulet
826466355	This amulet is intricately carved with a coat of arms.
826466356	HjorrMikill (Enhanced)
826466357	"HjorMikill' means GreatSword in an ancient language. 
Protected by the mountains and snow, this sword was probably forged for a King when the elders were young, to protect in troubled times."
826466358	Thunderer (Enhanced)
826466359	The unusual design of this heavy one-handed weapon appears to be of foreign origin. The air around the head of the weapon crackles with electrical energy.
826466360	"You were brave too, of course."
826466361	"Here, let me give you my father's amulet: it will protect you in your adventures."
826466375	Lothering has fallen! You wonder if Ser Arbither Cora's manor has been overrun too. Maybe you should pay her a visit?
826466377	Ser Arbether and Ser Bryant played their part in the Battle of Denerim. Both survived and they were subsequently married. Knife Edge has become a popular stopping off point for dwarven merchants.
826466378	"When Lothering fell to the darkspawn, Ser Bryant and his men were able to withdraw to Knife Edge. However they were unable to fight off subsequent darkspawn incursions, and the manor's defenders were all slaughtered."
855843158	The Valorous
855843159	"The Valorous is designed for the fashion conscious to show off their wealth and style in this aesthetically pleasing armor. Even in the battlefield, this lightweight armor is sure to draw the envy of many with its genuine gold studs delicately patterned across the fine polished leather."
954135869	Royal Aeducan Mace
954135870	"Bearing the Aeducan seal, this mace was crafted to enhance natural dwarven strengths and abilities."
954135874	Trian's Maul
954135875	The seal of House Aeducan is prominently displayed everywhere on this hammer. The mark of Smith House Turana is almost hidden on the handle.
954135882	High Morale Amulet
954135883	To simulate effect of non functional TRAIT_HIGH_MORALE
954135884	Low Morale Amulet
954135885	To simulate effect of non functional TRAIT_LOW_MORALE
954135991	Enchanter's Staff
954135992	"This staff thrills with power, having been invested with magic through rituals older than the Circle of Magi."
954136008	Werewolf Pelt
954136009	"The pelt of a werewolf, neatly skinned."
954136124	"<desc>Mandar Dace stands before you, defeated and staggering, awaiting the final blow.</desc>"
954136125	For the honor of House Aeducan!  <desc>Kill him.</desc>
954136126	Let all here witness that House Aeducan knows the meaning of mercy! <desc>Strike a nonlethal blow.</desc>
954136134	Paul (Qwinn) Escalona
954136135	"Qwinn's Ultimate Dragon Age: Origins Fixpack, by Paul (Qwinn) Escalona. v3.5

Fixes over 850 bugs in base Dragon Age: Origins.  Attempts to fix everything except combat mechanics and Awakening/DLC bugs.  Compatible with mods that affect only those, as well as texture/morph mods.  Enjoy!"
954136136	Qwinn's Ultimate DA:O Fixpack v3.5
954136169	Door
1070120002	Adds new spells to the Mage class that can magically open locks
1070120003	Beyond Ferelden
1070120014	"<name/> (<guitypename/>)
<usetype/>

<description/>"
1089623101	Peter 'weriK' Kovacs
1089623102	"It seems mysterious Ravens from far away lands appeared all over Ferelden. Who knows what they brought along…

This addin allows the player to unlearn all specializations, attribute points, spells or talents and skills they have spent on themselves or their companions."
1089623103	Character Respec Addon v1.6
1089623104	http://social.bioware.com/project/469/
1089623105	Potion of Respecialization
1089623106	"<title>Do not drink it!</title>
An exotic venom from far away lands erases good and bad memories alike."
1089623110	Potion of Respecialization
1089623112	Raven
1089623114	...
1089623115	There is a vial tied to the birds leg... <act>Try to take it!</act>
1089623116	<act>Leave the bird alone.</act>
1089623117	"Suddenly, you seem to know a lot more about ..."
1089623118	<act>Look into the raven's eyes</act>
1089623119	Assassin
1089623120	Bard
1089623121	Berserker
1089623122	Ranger
1089623123	Shapeshifter
1089623124	Spirit Healer
1089623125	Templar
1089623126	... especially the ways of the ...
1089623127	... especially the ways of the ...
1089623128	... especially the ways of the ...
1089623129	Warriors
1089623130	Mages
1089623131	Rogues
1089623137	Drink me!
1089623140	"Thank you for downloading Character Respecialization v1.6!
The module is now installed and working properly!"
1089623141	"! WARNING !
Respecializing your character can have unforseen implications! Always make sure that you have saved your progress before attempting to use this potion.

Are you sure you want to respecialize this character?"
1221411208	Plate of the Warden-Ensign
1221411209	"This distinctive armour bears the Grey Warden griffon, and was made for a standard-carrying junior officer of the order. While the design seems to favour mobility over protection it doesn't exactly lack either."
1221411210	Grey Warden Plate Boots
1221411211	These boots were made for stomping on the fallen darkspawn. Their massive weight lends itself well to this task.
1221411212	Grey Warden Plate Gloves
1221411213	"Thick metal plates have been bolted onto cuffs of these gloves, intended to provide each strike made with more impact."
1221411214	Grey Warden Robes
1221411215	"It's not uncommon for mages to find themselves amongst the ranks of the Grey Wardens. And while the price of admission is heavy, many choose to view it as the price of freedom."
1221411216	Grey Warden Gloves
1221411217	"These are long, elegant and supple, with faint runic patterns too elaborate to decipher easily."
1221411218	Grey Warden Boots
1221411219	"The Grey Wardens are no strangers to travel, and the care put into crafting these reflects that. Should keep the wearer going for as long as it's needed."
1221411224	Helm of the Warden-Ensign
1221411225	"The visor of this helmet vaguely resembles a griffon's beak. But other than that the design is quite featureless, compared to usual Grey Warden flamboyance."
1221411226	Plate of the Warden-Commander
1221411227	"Made for a high ranking officer of the Grey Wardens order. The design is somewhat outdated, but the craftsmanship of the highest quality."
1221411228	Helm of the Warden-Commander
1221411229	The unusually large griffon wings adorning this helm make it easy to recognize the wearer as a high ranking officer of the Grey Wardens.
1221411230	Grey Warden Leathers
1221411231	"We aren't judges. Kinslayers, blood mages, traitors, rebels, carta thugs, common bandits: Anyone with the skill and the mettle to take up the sword against the darkspawn is welcome among us."
1602176565	"Shale activates a mode that focuses on offense, taking penalties to defense and armor in exchange for bonuses to damage and attack. Slam, Quake, and Killing Blow add bonuses to this mode."
1602176566	"Shale slams a stony fist into the enemy target. If the blow connects, it generates an automatic critical hit and knocks the target back. The target is also stunned briefly unless it passes a physical resistance check. After learning this talent, Shale gains bonuses to damage, attack, and armor penetration whenever Pulverizing Blows is active."
1602176567	"Shale strikes the ground repeatedly, sending out multiple shockwaves. Nearby creatures take damage and are knocked to the ground unless they pass a physical resistance check. They are also slowed briefly unless they pass another physical resistance check. After learning this talent, Shale gains a bonus to movement speed, while suffering a greater penalty to defense, whenever Pulverizing Blows is active."
1602176568	"Shale focuses strength into one devastating blow against an enemy. This attack gains bonus armor penetration and is an automatic critical hit if it connects. If the target has less than 50% health, this attack inflicts increasing damage as the target’s health diminishes. Shale suffers penalties to attack and stamina regeneration for a short time after using this attack. After learning this talent, Shale gains bonuses to damage, attack, armor penetration, and critical chance whenever Pulverizing Blows is active."
1602176569	"Shale activates a mode that focuses on defense, gaining bonuses to armor, physical, and elemental resistances, while suffering penalties to damage and critical chance. Whenever this mode is active, Shale’s threat toward all nearby enemies increases over time, making them more likely to target Shale. Bellow, Stone Will, and Regenerating Burst add bonuses to this mode."
1602176570	"Shale erupts with the sound of the Rock itself, stunning nearby enemies unless they pass a mental resistance check against Shale’s constitution. They are also dazed, and suffer penalties to attack and defense, unless they pass another mental resistance check against Shale’s constitution. Enemies stunned by this attack cannot resist being dazed. The power of this talent depends on Shale's constitution. This talent increases the bonuses of Stoneheart."
1602176571	"Shale attracts the attention of a single enemy, who now views Shale as the most urgent threat on the battlefield and is likely to target Shale. After this talent is learned, Stoneheart will also give Shale bonuses to health regeneration and stamina regeneration, and enemies are even more likely to target Shale when that mode is active."
1602176572	"Shale explodes with energy, damaging all nearby enemies. Enemies hit by the explosion are knocked down or knocked back unless they pass a physical resistance check against Shale’s constitution. They are also stunned unless they pass a mental resistance check against Shale’s constitution. The energy gives Shale a burst of health regeneration and stamina regeneration. The lower Shale's health or stamina, the stronger the regeneration. The power of this talent also depends on Shale's constitution. This talent further increases the bonuses of Stoneheart."
1602176573	"Shale activates a mode that enables long-range attacks, gaining a large defense bonus against missile attacks while suffering penalties to attack and movement speed. While in this mode, Shale emanates an aura that grants nearby party members bonuses to ranged critical chance and ranged attack speed. Hurl Rock, Earthen Grasp, and Rock Barrage add bonuses to this mode."
1602176574	"Shale pulls a rock from the ground and hurls it to a location, dealing physical damage to all creatures in the impact area. Creatures closer to the center of the impact take more damage, and those within 3 meters of the center are also knocked down unless they pass a physical resistance check against Shale's strength. Friendly fire possible. This talent increases the bonuses for party members and Shale’s missile deflection."
1602176575	"Shale pounds the earth, immobilizing enemies unless they pass a physical resistance check, in which case they suffer penalties to attack speed and movement speed instead. Shale’s willpower increases the duration of the effects. This talent further increases Shale’s missile deflection."
1602176576	"Shale tosses up multiple rocks that crash down in the targeted area. Creatures within the area take damage and are knocked down or knocked back unless they pass a physical resistance check. Friendly fire possible. This talent increases the bonuses for party members and Shale’s missile deflection. Nearby party members now also gain bonuses to attack and damage when using ranged weapons. Additionally, Shale’s aura can now shield others, granting party members within 3 meters a bonus to missile deflection."
1602176577	"Shale activates a support mode that imbues nearby party members with bonuses to defense, armor, and all resistances. Shale is immobilized when in this mode, suffering a penalty to defense while gaining bonuses to armor, physical, spell, and elemental resistances. Inner Reserves, Renewed Assault, and Supernatural Resilience add bonuses to this mode."
1602176578	"Whenever Stone Aura is active, party members within the aura now receive bonuses to health regeneration, stamina regeneration, and spellpower. This talent also increases the radius of Stone Aura."
1602176579	"Whenever Stone Aura is active, Shale gains additional bonuses to armor, spell, and elemental resistances. Party members within the aura gain additional bonuses to health regeneration, stamina regeneration, and spellpower, as well as a bonus to movement speed. This talent also increases the radius of Stone Aura."
1602176580	"Whenever Stone Aura is active, Shale gains additional bonuses to armor, physical, spell, and elemental resistances. Party members within the aura gain additional bonuses to defense, armor, and all resistances. The aura now also grants additional bonuses to party members when they stay close to Shale. This talent also increases the radius of Stone Aura."
1602176581	Bonuses to damage and attack; penalties to defense and armor (Slam: bonus to armor penetration; Quake: bonus to movement speed).
1602176582	Knocked down; possible penalty to movement speed.
1602176583	Shale suffers reduced attack and stamina regeneration. Target is knocked down or knocked back.
1602176584	"Bonuses to armor, physical, and elemental resistances; penalties to damage and critical chance (Stone Will: bonus to health regeneration and stamina regeneration)."
1602176585	Stunned; possible penalties to attack and defense.
1602176586	"Shale gains increased health regeneration and stamina regeneration. Enemies are knocked down, knocked back, or stunned."
1602176587	"Shale gains increased missile deflection, but suffers reduced movement speed and attack. Party members gain bonuses to ranged critical chance and aim speed."
1602176588	Paralyzed; penalties to attack speed and movement speed.
1602176589	Knocked down or knocked back.
1602176590	"Shale is paralyzed but gains bonuses to armor and resistances. Party members gain bonuses to defense, armor, and resistances."
1602176591	Bonuses to ranged attack and damage; possible bonus to missile deflection.
1602176592	"Bonuses to defense, armor, resistances, and spellpower."
1602176593	Stone Will
1602176594	"With a will of stone, Shale becomes a living fortress. All active movement speed modifiers are immediately removed. For a time, Shale gains increased physical and mental resistances, and becomes immune to knockdown, knockback, and slip effects. All incoming damage is partially absorbed, until a maximum amount is reached. Shale is slowed during this time, but will also shrug off any incoming effect that would alter movement speed. The power of this talent depends on Shale's constitution. After this talent is learned, Shale gains bonuses to health regeneration and stamina regeneration whenever Stoneheart is active, and enemies are even more likely to target Shale."
1602176595	"Bonuses to physical and mental resistances; incoming damage is partially absorbed; immune to knockdown, knockback, slip, and movement speed modifications."
1602176596	"With a will of stone, Shale becomes a living fortress. All active movement speed modifiers are immediately removed. For a time, Shale gains increased physical and mental resistances, and becomes immune to knockdown, stun, and slip effects. All incoming damage is partially absorbed, until a maximum amount is reached. Shale is slowed during this time, but will also shrug off any incoming effect that would alter movement speed. The power of this talent depends on Shale's constitution. After this talent is learned, Shale gains bonuses to health regeneration and stamina regeneration whenever Stoneheart is active, and enemies are even more likely to target Shale."
1602176597	"Bonuses to physical and mental resistances; incoming damage is partially absorbed; immune to knockdown, stun, slip, and movement speed modifications."
